Ravi!
No, no, no...
Excuse me.
Where will I find Shekhar Home?
Shekhar?
-What?
-There is a girl here to see you.
They are behaving like they're
seeing a girl for the first time
like in a boys hostel.
Maybe they're seeing a
girl with you for the first time?
Oh, that...
is the just the way I am.
Alone...
and happy.
Should I leave?
Where? Oh no, I just...
What?
Oh, I see.
So you're using emotional
blackmail this time.
More interesting than that.
I have a case for you this time.
Do you believe in ghosts?
I... I don't mind
DAATGUNJ
Aunt Reena...
-Hemant?
-Yeah.
Mr. Home, Mr. Saini.
Thank you for coming.
I am Hemant and this is
my dad Sanjeev Bhaskar.
Sorry for your loss.
Who is that lady?
Kakoli.
She calls herself a tantrik(witch doctor)
but she is a fraud.
She opens shop every time
there is an unusual death.
What's Kakoli?
He won't spare anyone!
He won't spare anyone.
You will all die...
You will die.
You will die too man, you will.
You will die too.
You will all die!
He won't spare anyone.
Everyone will die.
-Everyone will die...
-Hey get lost! Get out of here!
He won't spare anyone.
BHASKAR VILLA
Please.
Wow...
This place looks
like a sofa showroom.
Really big.
This is your first
visit to Bhaskar Villa
and on such a terrible occasion...
The guy who died...
I mean, passed away...
How was he related to you?
Ravi uncle. My dad's younger brother.
Sarita aunty. Ravi uncle's wife.
His daughter Pakhi and
Aunt Reena.
Nice painting.
Very lifelike.
It feels like they are going
to come out and say hello.
Sorry...
So you guys aren't
originally from here, right?
Actually we have been
here for eight generations.
We are originally from Bilaspur.
We were coal merchants
who would take coal from Dhanbad and
sell it to the East India Company.
Since then the whole
family has always lived here.
So Ravi...
Why are you all standing? Please sit.
Make yourselves at home. Sit.
Please sit.
Sit Ms. Sarita, Pakhi...
Aunt Reena,
Sanjeev Bhaskar, how
did Ravi Bhaskar die?
Actually, two days ago
when we were having dinner...
everything was normal,
the mood was jovial,
and then Ravi uncle got
up to go to the washroom.
He was gone for 5 minutes
but when he came back
his behaviour was a bit...
weird.
What kind of behaviour?
Do you wear sarees or
do you not get the chance?
Dad, are you okay?
Ravi?
Are you okay?
He would have a drink every evening,
maybe he had a bit
too much that night?
I see.
And that same night Aunt Reena
heard something in the hall and
when she stepped out
of her room to check...
It looked like Ravi was running
away from something in fear.
When I saw him it looked like...
he might have seen him.
Um... Him who?
You know... him!
Sorry?
Skawndhokaata.
Did what?
Once he gets a hold of someone,
that person goes crazy.
And that craziness...
could drive someone
to kill themselves.
God knows how many such incidents
took place over the last 150 years--
This is why you're here.
This bullshit Skawndhokaata story.
You know the air, water and soil
in Daatgunj are mixed
with fear and superstition.
They say that someone
was sacrificed a long time ago
and his headless ghost
now wanders around.
And then every abnormal death
is blamed on Skawndhokaata.
Which is... Which is ridiculous!
And now my whole family thinks
that Ravi uncle was killed
by this Skawndhokaata.
Do you think I am lying?
Aunty... I didn't blame you...
Mr. Home, my uncle was
not killed by Skawndhokaata.
Please prove this to my family,
that's all I want.
An investigation cannot end
a 150-year-old superstition.
We appreciate you coming
because Hemant got another
chance to say what he wanted.
I am sure you must be tired.
Please rest here.
Then you can leave tomorrow.
Why wait till tomorrow?
We are ready to go back today.
You just need to show
us his post-mortem report--
Look, we don't do that here.
Hemant,
stop this nonsense.
Sanjeev uncle,
now that they are here
let them conduct an investigation.
Yes, please. Thank you.
Please?
So where is the dining room?
Should we go?
Who is this?
This is Manoj, our Estate Manager.
Please.
He is very young.
Give it to brother.
Ravi uncle just kept
walking into the water
and then he drowned himself.
How do you know these people?
Sanjeev uncle and
Hemant invested in my NGO,
we met because of that and
then we became friends.
And Ravi uncle who passed away?
Ravi uncle's whole family
lived in the US.
This was his first
visit in five years.
And then all of this happened.
And what about...
I am sorry for asking
so many questions.
Aunt Reena?
Aunt Reena is like
a mother to Hemant.
After Hemant's
mother passed away...
she never married.
She was the one who raised Hemant.
They're quite a lovely family.
They have given me a lot of love.
I have even performed
in this garden.
Oh.
Sanjeev uncle loves music
and Hemant is the opposite.
That's just how they are.
Hemant doesn't like music at all.
And musicians?
No... I...
Musicians...
only like other musicians.
The only thing Hemant is
passionate about is his plants.
He is a botany enthusiast.
He can spend hours
talking about his plants.
I can see...
the enthusiasm.
What could be so scary, Mr. Home,
that a man woke up and walked
into the pond to commit suicide?
Have you noticed the somber
mood of the whole village?
Let's find out partner.
Iraboty, let's go
meet the villagers.
Why? Why do you want to meet them?
-To find out more about Skawndhokaata--
-Skawndhokaata.
Again, this is why I told you.
The villagers believe that
talking about Skawndhokaata
is as good as inviting him.
Stay away from the villagers.
Do not insult their
beliefs and feelings.
Good morning.
Hi... have you seen Skawndhokaata?
The guy whose head was cut off?
You know Skawndhokaata?
=The one without...
Who didn't have...
Hey! Stop!
Uncle!
-Come with me.
-What?
Come with me.
Biren!
Shekhar?
Isn't that the guy who
said we would all die?
Sir, why aren't you taking the body
for post-mortem instead of this
superstitious nonsense?
This is the Daatgunj way.
These villagers won't
let me move the body.
Along with Skawndhokaata's prey.
How do you know that Skawndhokaata
was the one who killed him?
Hey Mahto, come here.
Tell him what you told me.
What are you doing sir?
You're wasting time!
You again?
Hey, lock this guy up.
Your police station...
comes under DIG
sengupta's jurisdiction, right?
-Yes.
-Do you want to hear it from him?
What?
Brother, why do you want to involve
the DIG in such a small case?
Please forget about it.
I will. Bring him down first.
It will be a big problem brother.
You are not from around here,
you can just leave.
We have to live here.
Is this how you fulfill your
duty even though you live here?
You don't know what you are doing.
And what are the
rest of you staring at?
He might be the one
committing the sin
but we will all have
to pay the price.
It will be a disaster!
Do something! Stop them!
Hey! Hurry up and remove
the body before they come back.
Come on hurry up. Move it.
Come on, let's go.
Hey wait! Go after them.
Run! Catch them!
-Run!
-That's what I am doing.
-This Iraboty will get us killed!
-They're throwing rocks, careful!
Forget about Skawndhokaata,
these villagers will kill us.
Go, go, go!
This Iraboty has made you go crazy,
why don't you choose safe
and high-paying jobs?
Go tell her. She is right there.
They're here.
How could you be so stupid?
-What now?
-Did you even think this through?
And you guys, are you happy now?
Now that the whole village is angry.
They can come all
the way to our home!
Brother's BP is rising.
What if he falls sick?
I will talk to them Aunty.
Ms. Reena, don't mind but
we are putting our lives in
danger to investigate this case
because Iraboty asked us to.
And this is the first time that
a victim of Skawndhokaata's
will get a post-mortem.
I think that's progress, you know?
Do me a favour and
don't leave this house!
Stay at home, that
is best for everyone.
And especially you!
Can I... freshen up?
Yes, please go.
You are unbelievable!
Shekhar!
Shekhar! No Shekhar! Shekhar stop!
No Shekhar! Stop it!
Have you come to
your senses, Partner?
Good morning.
Say "Thank you"
instead of "Good morning"
If I hadn't saved you last
night you would be dead.
I am sorry I got you into all this.
What happened last night?
Skawndhokaata.
Skawndhokaata?
It's real.
What?
Come on Shekhar...
Skawndhokaata is real.
We need to go back
to Biren's house.
But if Skawndhokaata is there,
then why are you talking
about going back there?
Because I won't go alone this time.
Will you take the army
and the police with you?
No that will take too long.
We will all go.
Carry a handkerchief
because that place stinks.
What were you doing outside
Biren's house last night?
Me? Not at all...
What do you know about Kakoli?
The same as everyone else.
She is a witch doctor
who reads horoscopes
and makes predictions, that's all.
But everyone knows that,
what do you know?
She is your good friend, right?
Why don't you show
me proof of that...
Ms. Reena I have a
lie detector in my head.
Whenever someone
lies the alarm rings.
It's very irritating.
I don't see Kakoli anywhere.
What are you looking for?
Let's look somewhere else.
Hey Kakoli!
No, no, no, let go of that.
Let go of that Kakoli!
I have called the
police and their staff
you gather the Bhaskar family.
Where are you going?
Chief guest...
to bring the Chief Ghost.
A 150-year-old superstition.
Ghosts and beasts.
Skawndhokaata.
Half alive and half dead
he would go straight for your head.
Well, I have a story
that's a bit tragic.
But it has varying degrees of pain.
The first pain
is a sweet pain.
It's the pain of love,
complete with a background score.
It's the pain of Bhaskar Villa's
Estate Manager Firdaus
and Reena's pain.
So? She liked him.
It was a one-sided love.
Once me and Ravi spoke to her,
Reena learnt her lesson.
Wrong answer.
You didn't speak to her.
You forbid her.
You scared and intimidated her.
Well, Aunt Reena gathered her broken
heart and faded into the background
and that is when a
new heroine entered.
Why are you digging up dead bodies?
Oh that reminds me!
That was a brutal murder.
Biren's murder by Skawndhokaata.
You know Pakhi,
Biren uncle was the
gardener at Bhaskar Villa.
And Firdaus' roommate.
And the other...
Heroine, right?
Swati.
Swati Bhaskar.
Sanjeev Bhaskar's wife.
She was in an abusive marriage.
Have you lost your mind?
Their pain was... the one with violins?
Hemant, what is this nonsense?
Why is he spewing lies
about your mother and I?
Let him speak!
Papa.
So, Swati found
her love in Firdaus.
But someone else
saw their love.
Right, Aunt Reena?
I obeyed my brothers.
I never stopped loving him.
That's true.
That is why you told
your brothers everything.
Ms. Reena told me...
Firdaus...
...the story of Firdaus and Swati.
You know Ms. Reena,
Swati and Firdaus had to
leave Daatganj because of you.
But they returned to
Daatganj two years later.
Why did they return
if they knew people
won't let them live here in peace?
Because family is family.
And a mother is a mother.
She came back for her son Hemant.
Then Aunt Reena
explained it to her brothers...
that it's fine.
Two years have passed.
Forget it and forgive them.
But you didn't forget, did you?
Fast-paced music plays here.
-To add some thrill.
-You have a son!
Hey! Come with us! Come on!
And Firdaus was killed.
I am sure you all know who
the villain is by now.
Then it is time
for the vamp to enter.
Kakoli.
Before she opened her shop with
Skawndhokaata's name
she used to read horoscopes.
Aunt Reena was her gold customer.
Now the villain has to do
something to avoid the police.
So they brought
Kakoli to their side.
You have to tell the villagers
that Skawndhokaata is back.
Keep it.
And that was how you
resurrected Skawndhokaata.
You even won Biren
over to your side.
And Biren told the villagers
that he saw Firdaus running away
from Skawndhokaata.
News confirmed and
the rumors spread.
Firdaus was killed
by Skawndhokaata.
You already know what
happened to your mother.
Overdose of sleeping pills.
She committed suicide.
So now the question is...
who killed Biren,
Kakoli and Ravi uncle?
Let’s ask Skwandhokata directly.
Right Manoj?
Manoj who became the Estate Manager
at such a young age.
You don't even have
hair on your face yet.
And you have already
committed three murders?
You have killed more people right?
Right? Before you joined here?
Am I right Manoj?
How many people have
you killed Manoj? Hey Manoj!
You're a serial killer Manoj.
Are you a serial killer Manoj?
Jayavrat!
Call the police and
take Manoj away.
Not Manoj...
Riyaz.
Riyaz, the cleft on your upper lip,
you have had that since
you were a child, right?
I saw a picture of
you at Biren's house
playing in Firdaus and Swati's lap.
Cute kid...
with a cleft.
I wanted to tell you something,
but don't tell anyone, okay?
Promise?
Promise.
Hemant...
you have a younger brother now.
Riyaz.
Look this is my son.
Oh my God, you even had a son!
He is with his aunt right now.
I will introduce him to you soon.
Mom passed away a few days later.
But I didn't forget Riyaz.
He was my brother.
It took some time...
but I found him.
And then a few years
later I brought him here.
With a new name.
Riyaz hasn't killed anyone.
This...
is the spicy twist in this story.
Radix pedis diaboli.
Devil's foot.
If anyone gets even
a whiff of its extract
they lose their minds.
And then
every person or thing they see
looks horrifying.
And there is only one
way to end that fear.
Suicide.
That is what all of
Skawndhokaata's victims did.
Suicide.
I was going to do it too.
Jayavrat saved me.
Growing the devil's foot
and removing its extract requires
a knowledge of botany.
And only one person
is that good at Botany here.
Right Iraboty?
The only thing Hemant is
passionate about is his plants.
He is a botany enthusiast.
And this botany enthusiast
got the extract from the plant.
Hemant knew when, how and where to
get his victims to smell the extract.
Well, we already know
who, how and why
Hemant killed them.
We have the murderer,
we have the motive,
and we have the proof.
Hemant?
After Ravi, Biren and Kakoli...
Was I next?
Kakoli is still alive.
Ms. Reena and
Kakoli told us the truth
and Kakoli is giving her
statement to the police.
What you and Ravi
uncle did to our mother
you deserve to be
punished for that.
Whether that might be going
to jail or dying by my hands.
You are my father
so I have made
arrangements for jail.
I always knew the whole story.
I just didn't have any
proof or witnesses.
Unfortunately Kakoli survived but
now she is ready to testify.
Thanks to Mr. Home
and his investigation.
And I hope that this will end
the reign of Skawndhokaata’s terror
that spread out across Daatganj.
Justice Chaudhary!
Come in.
You will find samples of Devil's
foot in Kakoli and Biren's blood.
Tell the whole village
that Skawndhokaata
was just a game, that is now over.
I am sorry.
Was I too harsh?
You have a good life young man.
When is your train?
In half an hour.
Are you thinking that you made
a mistake by calling me here?
I mean, they were
like a family to you
and I sent them off to jail.
Hemant wanted the truth to
come out and you helped him.
I did not make a mistake
by calling you here.
Well at least I have
one fixed client now.
You know, in the
future if there are any
blackmails or murderers, even a
theft is fine, you know who to go to.
-Shall we?
-Yeah.
-Bye.
Will we meet again?
Hi! Are you guys back?
Yes, I will just go freshen up.
You go too! Dirty...
See you soon partner.